{
    "id": "ace9edfba2a8464da5e4d29a92c29587",
    "title": "Identify The Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He walked out of the room without looking at anybody.",
            "description": "We make the simple past with the second form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple present",
                "simple past",
                "past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "335668f00df748308002814853964df1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is crying at the top of his voice.",
            "description": "We make the present continuous tense with be + ing form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple past",
                "present continuous",
                "present perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "361e807221b6412f808349231bffe8c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Small men never did great deeds.",
            "description": "We make the simple past with the second form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple present",
                "simple past",
                "past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f423ebbc548440bcb43fa6306c8a807d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never have betrayed my country.",
            "description": "We make the future perfect tense form with will have + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "present perfect",
                "past perfect",
                "future perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7c9da57ecd6545cabc09fea728762ae4"
        },
        {
            "question": "John has broken his leg.",
            "description": "The present perfect tense form is made with has / have + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple present",
                "present perfect",
                "simple future"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "645da72b1d3f4c52935a641c1d6ffde2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We need air and water to survive.",
            "description": "We make the simple present tense with the first form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple present",
                "simple past",
                "present perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e569623e98fb4257a468dd61b0ff1a42"
        },
        {
            "question": "This has been going on for a while.",
            "description": "We make the present perfect continuous tense with has/have + been + ing form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "present continuous",
                "present perfect continuous",
                "past perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "faf4207145ea45f6960c868679a3ae7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child was sleeping in his room.",
            "description": "We use the past continuous tense with was/were + ing form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple past",
                "past continuous",
                "past perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f44e3121c974941b2c658646b0f6999"
        },
        {
            "question": "They had already left.",
            "description": "The past perfect tense form is made with had + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple past",
                "present perfect",
                "past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2c0ce231295e4b9986030c39fabe6bbd"
        },
        {
            "question": "They had been waiting for hours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "past perfect",
                "past perfect continuous",
                "simple past"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "21c8f7e1177d44f8a6933cb907af2eb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She will arrive soon.",
            "description": "We make the simple future tense forms with will / shall + first form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple future",
                "future continuous",
                "future perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "427a3ef84bd04524aed2be9ddf548bc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "They will be having dinner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "simple future",
                "future continuous",
                "future perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "444a7cb97d874165920ce6d610431abe"
        }
    ]
}